here's a tutorial on how i use lifting
straps this is the technique that i use
to help me deadlift over 800 pounds i've
used it for over 15 years and i want you
to have it place your hands through the
straps and cinch them down so that they
form a v-shape around your thumbs the
tail and the loop should hang directly
down the center of your hands place the
heel of your hand on the bar and make
two wraps around wrap number one will
corkscrew outward towards your thumb
wrap number two will wrap back towards
your hand laying over the top of the
strap this locks the strap in place and
prevents the bar from rolling out take
your grip allowing for the tail end of
the strap to hang for you you should
feel as though all of the weight is
connected directly to your wrist it
takes time to get good at simultaneously
strapping both of your hands into the
bar practice twisting the bar until
they're both tight